[Music]
[SINGING]
(muffled singing)
(speaking in foreign language)
(whistling)
and not enough on a...
Today's footprint of him is we are just functioning there.
From far and even over,
God, everything that he's doing with
has certain questions.
And
what do you know really that?
Adam has to celebrate Adam and addicted from the heavens.
Similarly, Shaitan is to make a finite path taken in front of the heavens
and he was addicted from the heaven.
But the contraction of contrast here is that
[NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
He said, he can certainly hide.
My goal since it is your here that I know it's great.
I will entice and entice them because I need to tell them.
I'm third and this is not the mall.
So, when she tells purposeful how this works,
The first thing that is responding from the time given to the job is to find the way from the time that you have to go there.
Now, the importance of this, all our purposes on this earth, you can stop it for a lot.
And the only job you have to do is to... to submit yourself alone.
So, you did not create the heavens and earth and everything which is except for the purpose.
Our is truly coming.
So three times we deny the method.
And 86, the reward and position frame them.
And 51, verse 56, I have not created the genes and the humans
except the worshiping alone.
57, 57, I do not need any provision from them, or to any extent to people.
So anything we do is just for ourselves.
And our service on this road is to worship Allah alone,
This elaborate piece still is more. Here is 2*49, the verses between one and ten. It says that,
this is the religion secret to God, or mighty the wise.
We have revealed to you the secret truth war.
Accordingly, we shall worship God alone,
and we want worship, and no worship absolutely today.
To God, among shambied worship, those who
to send out idols recycling, saying, "We are idolizing them to bring us closer to God, God will join us, to feed them, to guard their speech, to guide their values and spirit."
with God one together of the country.
Now, we know that from these verses,
our purpose is to worship God alone,
and disregard anything that attributed to guidance,
which is supposedly a obvious and true man,
that by briefs, diversity can dispute among us.
Therefore, our third island is the Koran.
And the second thing is that we have to maintain righteousness
toward Allah and is being expected,
worse than the same to my servant who believe.
You shall maintain righteousness toward your Lord.
Those who are pious in this light
can be competitive therefore.
And God, Earth is special.
To stand fast, we will truly take down the next.
And the diversity in the 2014, the Algarfield before you, is in 2012 and those who speak will be told that the people of the United States are not able to do this.
that's a force to work in the inner greater than your opponent to work yourself.
The force we were invited to believe, because these truths were believed.
They will say, "Our Lord, we have given us to the two men and two lives.
We now confess our sins. We get anywhere out to them."
This is because when you invite a promotion,
rather long, you disagree.
When God says, "Profit yourself,"
they say, "You cannot be without a need,
"or without the strength of the prophets."
And they are in trouble.
When God says, "But when idols will mention
"besides you, believe, alas, the judgment can be decreased
by God, the most exalted and great.
This means 83 and 85.
Since evil satisfaction is inherited knowledge,
when their message is met to them in clear revelation,
they were satisfied with the knowledge they had,
Then when they saw our retribution, they said, "Now we believe in God alone, and we reject the idols we have set up.
But Allah's near to live is no more beautiful. Once they see our retribution, this is God's system that will never change the world.
These two rivers are always beautiful.
Another Himalayan view.
Let's see guys.
And under the left,
The first part of the proposal is we try to present some of the knowledge from the forearms,
the given eyes, and all the teachings of the Father God alone, without any process, without setting any eyes.
The second part that I was trying to make to some of my understanding is that we had to realize that the earth is just like that, it's a space to...
Now, when we set the satellite with the space of the Earth,
we give everything we provide.
That's the energy that's going to take even the energy
that any system can function.
We've heard everything is provided by God,
and everything is given by God.
We have to explore and utilize, modify for all purposes.
But, when we have said, the every said, from the heavens,
just because of this, this obedience to God, for God in the God,
I talked to him about the "Logan's Human Head" behind the "Logan's Human" by the same process. The "Shaytown" is perfect. He is just like Tom Ferely and Tom Ferely. He shows his own reasons.
not to accept the own world of God.
And the significance of peace is that in the Quran, also said that there are seven heavens, seven universities, and there are seven homes.
And they have a linear system over there, that's why I found a daily testing.
My feeling is that in the same parallel, if the others should have the same time,
or the same time, to diversate from the right hand.
So this means all the angels that brought in this God has to have very conscious
submission by God and they have had by God.
Now they have a test with the presence of God.
Physically we have a test with the knowledge of God given by his existence.
And probably the reason the end of the J-Tans was punished more severely than the end. So, oh, I think that's it.
Therefore, we know that God is Almighty is one, and the only thing is we have to fulfill
the sub-mix alone, and follow the writers.
And once we have something to ourselves, we say our ego is killed, then we are ready
to give a vision to him and to follow his act.
Shala Allah Allah in the makeup. Since you're nervous and following this head play. With head play. And Shala in the skin. Put it on the other side. No one will know about what you're doing.
(indistinct chatter)
(gavel bangs)
(crowd chattering)
(crowd talking)
(iokbody shouting)
(crowd chattering)
(s Food street chatter)
(children laughing)
(crowd chattering)
(laughing)
(indistinct chatter)
(chatter)
[Laughter]
(distant
a
Our family are locked. The one that has no guidance that he believes that he deserves to be the citizen.
Hopefully, from the previous district, there's no need to deal with the full aid of justice.
Previously, the graduate people, who did deal with that report, those who just need the guidance and regulations, have to be done so much to be.
That is all my ability.
Nothing is ever to feel for that, or earth or in the heavens.
Here is the one who changed me aside to whom they're easier.
There is no kind of justice to all my divine.
Here is the one who revealed me just quickly.
This touch of person has one who saved the living.
But they have the touch of them to answer such a story.
Those who are in their hearts, the world of the algorithms,
the creation of the experiment, and the misrepresentation.
There are no one knows the differentiation.
They are the step-dad.
And those world-founding in those.
They say, we believe in all the recommendations.
They all come from our Lord.
Indeed, only those who progress in television
can be our Lord.
Then none are high as false, but after being done by you.
And some of you can let you out of the ground.
Our Lord, you will surely gather all the people of the day
that is in heaven, but God never breaks his tongue.
Those who just believe neither their money nor their children
the sheriff and the guest guy. They will be true of the hero. Like the people of Pharaoh, the early people of the rejected our brother base.
God comes just a very clear guy is strictly important. Right. To those who just believe you will be deceived.
They end up in here. They're a miracle of hope.
Well, I guess that's enough.
Okay.
Okay, my understanding says,
maybe I'll know this.
First, what?
I was going to leave.
It's part of the economic initiative
from the Mississippi that, from the near to the post,
there's been a mere bill
And the competition that you can do is be seated.
And if you read the piece, you can read the difference.
And it's not going to turn left to right.
It helps to explain how it's going to be solved.
This is provided for a time.
It's an obvious thing.
And two, very, very, very, very, very hard to be on here.
And three, and we saw that with the staff.
Three, just to try to tell the audience that you can deal with this,
this group of students, and we've decided all the others to do.
I just probably do have a clear topic that different people can understand.
I was in the middle of this region, whatever you want,
it's like a television.
You are all up where,
only in the first time you tell me that they believe
that this surrounded the strictly in faith.
So this is the matter,
the time all the strictly there
came down in the corner from beginning to end.
And then you know, this is the time it's living.
And it's a guy that teaches for all of you.
And I guess it's my understanding that we can direct it to the agenda, but before all the people. And those who believe, who just believe, that is the reason that we do.
[ Inaudible ]
Alarmos, so we can wear a mask.
Alarmos, everything you do.
So, whether you do winter or weather,
because you can speak with it,
Alarmos, you don't have to attempt to do it.
Now, I'm feeling patient.
So, you can wear a mask, so keep your back in mind.
Whether you do normal or am I a patient?
a full country of this kind of a no-made and no-eye or whatever you want to change their people.
And there is no bad attempt to be.
And he is the only real, real, too stupid.
Like a lot of people make things that are because of the shining man, the burning.
And the fact that it's the time for where she tells you to be out of the ground and it's just the past.
And they have something to do.
And the first term to teach you is the Alabama Union.
It has to be part of the year of the day.
And it makes you also know that there's a craft that may not be past.
And then it's also something that a lot of people try to make the treatment so it's to try because he is the among people on the mountain.
And he is the one that guide you to bring the food.
But that was the reason we used to speak with a force in the leader's eye.
So this is the word of God.
And the man who shot even though God used God,
the leader told me that he was born and kept using those guns.
And I hunted him out of the flesh and he had to do with his hands.
and you're helping us, you can't tell us to really spread the voice to our bottom line.
And then those who got down to the house,
will sometimes get struck on scripture that our world,
and if they can't see what's on the ceiling,
and they get struck on it and they'll get taken on,
You know, take a little wait from the whole country
of what the country is saying.
And so they're expecting to meet because it's on how
we can't obtain right now that we want to obtain it.
And so being able to obtain it,
you know, they think that it's hard to do it anymore.
Just come over to our own machine,
and wherever it is, and leave it alone
I said, "Just a minute."
And somebody said, "No one really wants to correct
"inconcipation of the United."
Except that.
But it's also stand two days,
going to be those that have found their knowledge.
Like the shot of these other governments,
and I know two that have their own knowledge.
I'm going to say that you're some understanding of what it's doing.
But what are the guidelines, the law of the media, at least?
It's an understanding of safety.
And it's saying that those who take heed to that mentality,
we need a one-year-old girl who's going to be in trouble.
And he's taking the blood, and he's going to be in trouble.
But you must be in trouble, and you must be in trouble.
And then first eight to tell you that one like,
"I think they got it to this place."
- You got it? - "They're being asked a lot,
"to continue to guide, and tell the mercy of the man."
And I think that's what you make your teeth clear.
And nine, there is no, I'm more.
You will surely gather all the people who say they are irrelevant.
But God never brings the plan.
And thereby just going to steal anything, anything, nothing,
takes longer on the times of life.
God never brings the plan.
And he says to me,
to me,
I make sure he has the time to steal earth.
And it's like anything to ask.
And I know that this time that we have to be here, and to live, in order to get that time, and come down.
And those who just leave, either have money nor you should, will help them get down, like a personal food deal and what it might be on you.
And some folks, how many people have a hundred,
some help here.
And when you drive, they know nobody is here to help.
You know, they're there to help.
And that's the problem.
It's just the reason for how they will be coming.
They're talking about the history of the economy.
And they're there to see it.
And they're trying to find it.
I'm trying to abandon this feeling.
I'm trying to abandon all the colors.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
>> Mr. Harsh, thank you very much.
>> I'll give you more stuff from this again, I'll give you a thank you.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
We have to put North, uh, in the living somewhere in the end.
To see if there's no two-one and offended one,
the miraculous significance of this ironic mission.
After fourteen hundred years, the mystery of this message is now on place.
We fought in eight chapters, eight sorrows that these lessons are the nerveiness of the
one.
They were a mysterious, we made mysterious folks, talking from the years.
And God taught us that the other is a secret.
that there is a secret in Iran that will be unveiled in the future, not in the Hamid's
time.
So these letters are the vertical Quran.
It was these letters and the vertical associated with them that I personally use as a sign
that this translation is authorized by God.
As a chemist, I had no business classification with the law.
And I refused to publish it.
I did it for myself, in each year.
Put some economics back then.
Sell check.
Drama!
presented getting all the make options today.
Okay.
Now I am going to apply for speaker Zackny.
(clicking)
[ Pause ]
(silence)
(clicking)
[ Pause ]
(silence)
[ Silence ]
(clicking)
(silence)
[ Pause ]
I have to do the assignment. I refuse to publish this. I have anything to do with it unless there is a definite time that I have also liked to do this.
Now 1400 years now I'm going to look at it. It's very simple.
But nobody ever found it. It's all over the front. It's throughout the front.
Nobody ever saw it. So this one is different, they are signed and they went from different footnotes to one.
So when anyone attacks this translation to you, you can show them this footnotes to one.
And you can ask them, "What about this letter?
Whoever who found the thin garden, just pick out any one to let them discover the American of God."
Discover the American of Para. Anyone who does not know.
(sound of device observable)